<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Yves Vandewoude's personal site]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Yves Vandewoude's personal site]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/yves-vandewoude-s-personal-site/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 15:44:47 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/yves-vandewoude-s-personal-site/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[
Welcome to my website!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>
Welcome to my website!</h1><p>I'm a software engineer & architect based in Leuven, Belgium. In 2001 I graduated from the KULeuven with a master in computer engineering (Burg. ir. Computerswetenschappen). I then proceeded on the path towards a PhD, a goal I accomplished in march 2007 with a thesis on dynamic software evolution. I stayed at the DistriNet research group as a Post-doctoral researcher for another two years, during which time I was responsible for a number of software architecture related projects with the industry. Together with two collegues, I founded my own company named Qmino in August 2008 and have been working there full time since september 2009.

In my spare time, I'm an avid traveller, movie-fan, play magic-the-gathering, channel my aggression into a squash-ball once a week and I read a lot of books.

On my website, you can find information about both my professional and leisure activities.

Enjoy!

Yves</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/d9a322386b7e975551422e56fe26d30fcbff56e3.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/yves-vandewoude-s-personal-site/6672c3d8-21f8-40ff-9ff8-751eb5acba74/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6672c3d8-21f8-40ff-9ff8-751eb5acba74</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 14:10:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personal]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Personal</h1><p>I was born on February 9th, 1978 in Wilrijk (Belgium). I spent my elementary and highschool years at the Onze-Lieve Vrouwecollegein Antwerp from which I graduated in 1996 with a degree in Latin-Mathematics. My most important hobby at that time was Judo, which I also thaught to small children (age 5-9). I also played the flute for a few years. My intrest for both hobbies faded when I left for university, and although I have considered restarting Judo, I haven't found the time so far. In 1996, I left the beautiful city of Antwerp to continue my education at the University of Leuven from which I obtained a master in computer engineering (June 2001), Bachelor in Economics (September 2006) and a PhD in Applied Science: Computer Science (March 2007). As a computer engineer, one of my primary hobbies is of course computers and everything that surrounds them. I'm also an avid traveller and try to leave Europe at least once every year and see a lot of movies, both from my own DVD collection and in the theatre. I play squash, read a lot and, last but not least, enjoy playing magic the gathering immensely although I do find myself stressed for time more and more since I started working at Qmino.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/yves-vandewoude-s-personal-site/c23dbe09-03bf-4ad1-be7e-30ccbdc3f5af/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c23dbe09-03bf-4ad1-be7e-30ccbdc3f5af</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 14:11:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Qmino]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Qmino</h1><p>Qmino was founded by Peter Rigole, Bert Vanhooff and myself in 2008. We are a software development firm and develop complex tailor-made software for our customers, typically with a complex backend.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/cd34daed1045e43d9feb2b2cb38f85df88745b6e.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/yves-vandewoude-s-personal-site/qmino/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">226a620c-9f26-4ebc-80e1-daa663c16c20</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 15:44:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>